Say your prayers.
God Is a Bullet is a thriller, action, crime film directed by Nick Cassavetes.
Vice detective Bob Hightower finds his ex-wife
murdered and daughter kidnapped by a cult.
Frustrated by the botched official investigations, he quits the force and infiltrates the cult to hunt
down the leader with the help of the cult’s only female victim escapee, Case Hardin.
Case, played by Maika Monroe.
Bob Hightower, played by Nikolaj Coster-Waldau.
Cyrus, played by Karl Glusman.
Maureen Bacon, played by January Jones.
The Ferryman, played by Jamie Foxx.
Sgt John Lee Bacon, played by Paul Johansson.
God Is a Bullet is a 2023 American action thriller film written and directed by Nick
Cassavetes and starring Nikolaj Coster-Waldau, Maika Monroe, and Jamie Foxx.
It is based on the 1999 novel of the same name by Boston Teran.
God Is a Bullet was released in the United States by
Wayward Entertainment on June 23, 2023.
The tone is intense.